

WEB DEVELOPER · FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER · FUUL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Adelaide, Australia

□ (+61) 410 256 252 | woleksii.mostovyi@gmail.com | # www.oleksiimostovyi.com | □ olimstv | □ olimstv

"Experience is the only thing we can truly own in our lives..."

Summary

A software developer with a background in automation testing.

I genuinely believe that our World can become much better if every living being had the most positive life experience. I see tremendous opportunities to contribute to the improvement of people's life experiences by developing software solutions. Therefore I would love to join a team of like-minded people, where I can effectively grow and apply my professional and personal skills to benefit the community.

Skills

Front-end HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Next.js, Gatsby.js

Back-end Node.js, Express, REST API, Ruby, Rails

DatabasesMongoDB, SQL, PostgreSQLDevOpsHeroku, AWS, Docker, JenkinsLanguagesEnglish, Ukrainian, Russian

Work Experience __

General Assembly

Australia

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Nov. 2020 - present

During the course I have built a number of projects using different technologies stacks. The most mature of them is Resume Builder App - The open-source web application for fast and easy creation and publishing (with unique public URL) of resumes 'tailored' for each particular vacancy.

- lets.Get(IT) built using React, Next.js, MongoDB. Building this application, I've learned that integration of different technologies into one app might be challenging, but also it gives a significant improvement of developer's skills and knowledge base
- Memo a simple notes-gathering app, built with React and Ruby on Rails, using PostgreSQL database. Learning how to build a backend using Ruby on Rails has broadened my perspective as a developer
- CountLess a budget app that helps track incomes and spending. Main focus for this project was building backend. I learned how to protect routes, how to use Passport is package and a basics of SSR using Handlebars

Relocation Australia

Feb. 2019 - Nov. 2020

During this period (after moving to Australia), I put all my efforts into settling on the new place, learned a new culture, and embraced a commitment towards change and personal development. I continued my self-education in Software Development until I decided to take a leap and enrolled in a Full Stack Software Engineering Immersive course of General Assembly

GlobalLogic Lviv, Ukraine

SOFTWARE TESTING AUTOMATION ENGINEER

Nov. 2017 - Feb. 2019 and Sep. 2015 -

Jun. 2017

- Testing software for a medical device (insulin pump), utilizing a custom set of frameworks and libraries, using JavaScript language.
- Writing test scripts and test scenarios to meet acceptance criteria and quality standards
- Performing formal testing to provide the results for the Federal Drug Administration (FDA)
- Automated test code-review and test stabilization
- Reviewing design inputs according to the scope of testing issues
- Creation and updating of UI and Functional Test Cases (manual and automation)
- System components and functions analysis
- · Performing iteration analysis and test planning
- · Participation in knowledge-sharing activities

Rolique Lviv, Ukraine

Quality Assurance Test Engineer

Jul. 2017 - Nov. 2017

- Testing of a CRM web application for the "INTERMATE Media GmbH".
- · Manual testing of the developing features and regression testing, writing product, and test documentation
- · Analyzing client requests for validity and feasibility
- Documenting results of test execution and bug reporting
- Performing fortnightly demos for presentation to the product owners

QALight Kyiv, Ukraine

SOFTWARE TESTING AUTOMATION ENGINEER

jun. 2014 - Sep. 2015

Testing a Social Event Discovery Platform – a web-based platform that delivers content and information on entertainment and business events within Europe.

Primary responsibilities: manual testing of the developing features and regression testing.

- · Analyzed business requirements and suggested improvements to the product features
- Developed test cases for functional and regression testing of the project Actify
- · Validated application's GUI for compliance with Usability guidelines published by US Department of Human Services

Education

General Assembly Australia Australia

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING IMMERSIVE

Nov. 2020 - May. 2021

• Full Stack Web Development course

QA Light Training Centre

Kyiv, Ukraine

SOFTWARE TESTING AND QUALITY ASSURANCE

Dec. 2014 - Jul. 2015

- Software Testing and Quality Assurance
- Networking
- SQL

Donetsk Music College Donetsk, Ukraine

Bachelor of Music Sep. 2003 - Jun. 1007

- Music Art
- · Music Teacher
- Percussions
- Brass Opchestra
- · Symphony Orchestra

Interests & Passions _____

Music Professional musician, Drummer, Music teacher, Sound Engineering, Video Production

Psychology Neurophysiology, Psycho-analysis, Behavioral Psychology, Cognitive Psychology

Philosophy Stoicism, Vedic Philosophy, Buddhism, Zen